This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Encouraged by Dark King Rayleigh, Luffy overcame his sorrow
and returned to the site of his brother's death.
While there, he both paid respects and delivered a secret message to his crew.
One by one, they received it through the newspaper.
Normally, Luffy wouldn't do something like this.
There's gotta be a catch here.
I got it, Luffy!
Don't worry!
I'm changing plans, Dad!
Yeah!
Okay!
So that's it.
Very well, then.
Roger that, Captain.
Yes, Luffy!
Yes!
But honestly, Luffy, how about how I feel, huh?
You're so selfish.
I got you, boss.
Ah-ha.
How very clever of you.
No need to worry, Luffy.
See you in Sataoni in two years!
Luffy's training begins!
To the place we promised in two years!
There he is.
Hey, Jinbei!
Thank you for everything!
No, Luffy!
Please!
It is I who should be thanking you!
When we met at Impel Down, I begged you.
I said I would put my life on the line for Ace.
And yet your brother died while I still live.
Please forgive me.
You did all you could've done.
Don't beat yourself up.
If it weren't for your help, I probably wouldn't have made it into Marine Ford in the first place.
You can be prepared for your help.
I know.
You know.
You're right as always.
And who can say, one day there may still be something I can do to help you on your journey.
Until then, see you on Fishman Island in two years.
Be sure to bring your entire crew along.
I look forward to meeting everyone.
You got it.
Take care, TJ!
Luffy, I'm so glad that you're back to your old self.
A twinkle in your eye.
That smile.
Charming, confident, and carefree.
Just seeing your face has put my heart aflutter.
I'm weak in the knees.
My goodness, I could almost die.
I'm dizzy.
Hey, Hancock.
You okay?
Yes.
Yes, of course I am.
Pardon my manners, but could you take us to the island now?
I'd like to begin Luffy's training as soon as possible.
Yes, certainly.
Kuja, set sail for Ruskaina!
Aye, aye, Snake Princess!
This island will be perfect.
It has 48 seasons a year, so you'll constantly have to adapt to the harsh conditions.
Whoa!
Sounds neat!
Oh, Luffy!
While you're here, I'll be sure to bring you the most delicious food from Amazon Lily every day.
Doesn't that sound nice?
Yeah!
Thanks, Hancock!
You rock!
Let's see, could you start off with that specialty gorgon something or other?
That stuff's really good.
Why, yes, of course!
Yay!
That's our princess!
I'll bring you anything you desire, and as much of it as you want.
Oh, my!
I do believe he's uttered my name at least ten times now.
That must mean we're engaged!
No, it doesn't!
And didn't you say a little while ago that you were married?
Foolish girl doesn't even know the proper order of things.
No, Hancock.
Sorry, but I just can't have you spoiling him.
His sole purpose here is to train.
He can't let distractions get in the way.
What?
Huh?
You have got some nerve, old man.
Luffy has the right to decide that.
You got it!
And be careful how you respond.
I can turn you to stone!
There are plenty of things to eat here.
Luffy needs to hunt for himself.
That's part of the training.
You'll ruin his nose, Snake Princess!
If he can't get by with roughing it for a while, then maybe he shouldn't be a pirate.
This is all for Luffy's benefit.
Huh?
Luffy?
Then this will help him become stronger.
Yes, it will.
If this is all for Luffy.
Then I'll be patient!
Mm-hmm.
But Rayleigh, this island is truly dangerous.
If anything should happen to him.
That's why it's an ideal place to train him.
If you're that worried, make a wish on a star.
Are you ready, Luffy?
Sure am!
Goodbye, Luffy! It's been fun!
Don't get killed, okay?
Bye!
Luffy, take care of yourself.
You'd better remember this tree.
Even the most savage beasts stay away from it.
It's the only safe area on this island.
I don't think I'll forget it.
It's pretty funny looking.
And another thing to know, you may have guessed, but we're the only humans on this entire island.
Behold the vast wilderness.
Supposedly there was a country here a long time ago.
But as you can see, the humans lost the struggle for survival.
The land is rough, and nature relentless.
Oh!
This place smells like adventure!
The island is crawling with vicious creatures.
Far too many to be counted.
Now, by my estimation, there's about 500 animals you don't stand a chance of defeating yet.
Unless you become stronger, you might even get killed in your sleep.
How do you know so much about this place?
Did you used to live here?
Yes, as you will.
And you'll obtain the same power I did then.
Huh?
The power known as hockey.
Hockey.
Hey, watch out!
There's a huge thing behind you!
What are you doing?
Don't just stand there!
Listen to me, Luffy.
Believe it or not, hockey is a latent power that everyone has within themselves.
Wow!
I think it's a giant elephant!
Like five times the normal size!
Observation.
Fighting spirit.
Intimidation.
Hockey is really no different from any combative instincts normal humans have.
However, most of them live their lives without tapping into their true potential,
because they don't have a teacher like you do now.
You mustn't have any self-doubt.
Only then will you become stronger.
Run away!
Time for second gear!
Jetcastle!
Damn it!
This guy's no joke!
He's super fast for as big as he is!
Now watch very carefully.
There are two prominent types of hockey used in battle.
Get out of there!
Don't worry.
The elephant will try to hit me with its trunk coming in from the right side.
First is the power to feel the presence of others more strongly.
This is known as observation hut.
No way!
If you enhance this power, you can even tell where unseen enemies are located.
You can determine how many there are and predict what their next moves will be.
Really?
That left kick won't work.
Mantra.
On Skypiea, it has a different name.
There, it's called Mantra.
Oh!
Dammit!
Next, the armor mataki.
Think of it as covering yourself in invisible armor.
Riley, no!
No!
That move!
I've seen it before!
Has she got it, Dokoi?
Armor that's hard enough can even be used as a weapon.
Hey!
I shouldn't be able to feel that!
I made out a rubber!
Consider it another benefit of knowing how to use this haki.
Unless they have a specific weak point, those with devil fruit powers are hard to hit.
Armament haki provides the only other effective countermeasure against such enemies.
Take those with logia-type devil fruits.
Their body composition makes them seem impossible to touch,
but armament haki has the power to strike them.
Ah, so that's how you were able to hit Kizaru.
Interesting.
That kind of haki might be able to punch Smokey or Aokiji or anybody.
You can also transfer armament haki to a weapon.
Have you ever seen the Kuja Pirate's arrows?
I have.
It was like they were made out of steel.
Observation and armament.
They're the two main types of haki.
However, there are some people in this world who can use another type of haki.
Watch closely.
Huh?
Uhr...
The power to intimidate your enemies into submission.
This is Conqueror's Hockey.
The most well-known legends of the Grand Line.
They often have the rare Conqueror's Hockey at their disposal.
However, although you can control the Conqueror's Hockey,
unlike the other types, there's no way to train yourself to use it.
The Conqueror's Hockey embodies the spirit of the owner himself.
Strengthen your spirit and you strengthen its power.
Hey! That's what you did at the auction house!
Everybody just passed out!
Ah, so you already know what it is.
Then again, that's not very surprising.
You have the power as well.
Don't you die!
Conqueror!
Hmm. Here's a tip.
Don't use Conqueror's Hockey until you can handle it,
as in fully control it.
Or otherwise, you'll end up overwhelming innocent people
who get caught in the action.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Amazing!
No wonder you were his first mate!
You can knock out half your enemies
without even laying a finger on them!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I guess I was tougher than you thought.
Ha!
Actually, wait!
I just realized
I've seen all sorts of people use Hockey.
There's Shanks, Grandpa,
Eneru, Isa, and Hancock,
plus her sisters and all the Kuja warriors.
This is true.
But still, learning how to use Hockey
is no easy task.
Huh?
Usually, we'd need a lot more time to train right.
But thankfully, you're qualified.
Here's how it'll work.
Start with the basics.
In two years' time,
I'll teach you how to use all three types,
even Conqueror's Hockey.
Most users tend to focus on one type,
or rather they play to their strengths
if they don't have the talent
to master every single art.
That's fine for them,
but I think you'll want to aim
much higher than that.
And if you can develop all three,
you'll have so much more at your disposal.
Uh-huh.
All right, fine.
Well, then.
I'm now officially your trainer.
Don't think for a second
I'll go easy on you.
Yeah?
Give me everything you got.
Huh.
All right, let's begin.
Oh, just one last thing.
Huh?
If I remember right,
the old man said this tree
is the only safe place.
For two years,
I'll disappear from the world
and hang up my hat.
Here.
Ace, Luffy, listen.
The three of us,
we're going to leave this country.
We're going to sail the seas
and see the world.
And we're going to have
lots of adventures.
We'll be pirates!
I'll be so tough
that all the other pirates
and all the marines
will bow at my feet.
Everyone in the world
will know my name.
That's going to be the legacy
I leave behind when I die.
Then I know
what I'm going to be, too.
The king of the pirates!
Oh, almost forgot.
The fever card.
Everybody.
Luffy.
Luffy?
Luffy!
Luffy.
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy!
Oh, hey, Luffy!
Come on, Luffy.
Hurry it up.
Let's get started.
Be right there.
Okay, old man!
Let's do it!
Hmm.
First off,
don't call me old man.
Call me Sir Rayleigh.
Or how about Professor Rayleigh?
Maybe Master Rayleigh?
Gotcha!
Thanks, old man Rayleigh!
Fine.
Pleasure
な!
handc Hari
ありakers
ありestaけの夢をかきあつね
I mean buying them hard as well
One piece
Last paper
It's just a tank
Everyone is where the color is
And we'll
take that
Ohiten
You can just
確かめたのなんだ 伝説じゃない
個人的な話は 誰かの場合を
リズムの勝手 思い過ごせばいい
ありったけの夢をかき集め
探し物を探しに行くのさ
トケットの恋 それさ you're gonna be my friend
We are, we are on a coast
We are
Hey Zoro and Usopp, Sanji and Nami, Chopper, Robin, Frankie, Brooke
And Ace and Sabo, I'm making you guys another promise
I'll get stronger no matter what it takes
We are
Two years after the War of the Best
The Straw Hat crew finally returns to Saboori
However, the archipelago has changed
And with dangerous pirates lurking around in droves
Their departure to the new world may not go as smoothly as they hoped
On the next One Piece, the beginning of the new chapter
The Straw Hats reunited
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Like I'll be king of the new , if you uhh